francethisway.com 2018-12-25

# Privacy

We use the minimum cookies possible on this site to enable us to provide a satisfactory user experience and provide relevant advertising, but these can also be blocked if you prefer. This is easiest if you block them in your browser and with the Your Online Choices site (see below) but there are other options if you prefer (also listed below).

## Personal information and cookies

A cookie is a piece of information that a website puts on your computer so it can remember something about you or your device at a later date. We use cookies to distinguish you from other users of our site. This helps us to provide you with a good experience when you browse our site. We also use cookies to show you personalised advertising.

For more information about cookies see [Cookies (wikipedia)](https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/HTTP_cookie).

You can check the cookies that our site uses (as well as the cookies used by other sites) at <http://www.cookie-checker.com/>

## Our use of cookies

We use a session cookie to monitor your progress on the site: this has no personal information about you and is used to improve your experience during a visit. It expires as soon as the visit is finished.

We do need to use a cookie on your computer to remember that you have 'accepted' the privacy policy, otherwise you would have the message obscuring the text on every page, every time you visit.

## Third party use of cookies

We store no personal information about our visitors and have no access to personal information about our visitors.

Cookies are used by Google on our site with Google analytics and Google adsense to help enhance your experience and to help us to offer a better service to future visitors. These cookies record, for example, how long 'a visitor' spent on a particular page or on the site, or how often visitors come back to the site a second time, and allow personalised advertising.

Because we share information about your use of our site with Google the following links may be useful to you:

  * for information on how Google uses this data visit <https://policies.google.com/technologies/ads>
  * to change your personal settings on google see <https://myaccount.google.com/?hl=en>

## Personalised ads

Under GDPR rules introduced in May 2018 everyone in Europe has the right to restrict access to their private data and prevent adverts being shown that are based on monitoring their online activity.

  * See [Google Ads Settings](https://adssettings.google.com/authenticated) for information about how to opt out of personalised ads from Google
  * See [Your Online Choices](http://www.youronlinechoices.com/uk/your-ad-choices) for information about how to opt out of personalised ads from other ad agencies in the EU or [aboutads.info](https://www.francethisway.com/aboutads.info) in the US.

## Data sharing

Under the Google EU User Consent Policy we must identify each ad technology provider that receives end users' personal data as a consequence of your use of a Google product, and provide information about the use of that data. Ad technology providers use this data, for example, to show you personalized adverts.

The following is currently the only ad technology provider that might receive users' personal data in this way from this site, and their associated privacy policy page (where you can opt out of this use):

  * Criteo <https://www.criteo.com/privacy/>

## Google analytics

Many sites including this one use google analytics because it is very useful for monitoring trends in visitor behaviour, but if you prefer that your data is not used by google analytics you can prevent its use.

See <https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout> for details.

_IP anonymization is turned on in our google analytics accounts: your IP address is not recorded by google or ourselves and can not be personally identified with you._

## Disabling all Cookies

You can prevent the setting of all cookies on your computer by adjusting the settings on your browser. Disabling cookies altogether will affect the functionality of this and many other websites that you visit, therefore it is recommended that you do not do this, but it is always an option. See the following help pages depending on which browser you are using:

  * Firefox <https://support.mozilla.org/en-US/kb/enable-and-disable-cookies-website-preferences>
  * Internet Explorer <https://support.microsoft.com/en-us/help/17442/windows-internet-explorer-delete-manage-cookies>
  * Google Chrome <https://support.google.com/chrome/answer/95647>
  * Safari <https://support.apple.com/kb/ph21411>
  * Iphone and Ipad <https://support.apple.com/HT201265>
  * Android Chrome <https://support.google.com/chrome/answer/95647>

## Privacy Policy

The privacy of our visitors is of extreme importance to us. If you require any more information or have any questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to contact us by email at [francethisway@gmail.com](mailto:francethisway@gmail.com) .
